pomsinoz.com 2016-12-01

# Pomsinoz Privacy Policy

**POMSINOZ.COM PRIVACY POLICY**

For the purposes of this page, [ www.pomsinoz.com](http://www.pomsinoz.com/) will be referred to as the 'Forum'

We are committed to safeguarding your privacy online. This privacy policy applies to your information that we collect and receive; it does not apply to practices of businesses that we do not own or control or people we do not employ. At no time will we sell your information or release your personally-identifiable data without your permission. You can visit this Forum without revealing who you are or providing any personal information about yourself.

By using this Forum, you agree to the terms of this privacy policy. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you use our services. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices.

This Forum contains links to other websites. These include links to resources in related topics and third-party websites that offer other related products. If you visit another website through a link on our Forum, please consult the privacy policy of the website you are visiting. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites that you may visit.

**Browsing the Forum**

If you browse through the Forum without entering any personal data, we will gather and store certain information about your visit. This information does not identify you personally and cannot be linked back to you unless you decide at some point to identify yourself. If you are only browsing, we collect the following information: IP address, the type of browser and operating system used to access our Forum, the date and time you access our Forum, the pages you visit (click-through), and if you arrived at our Forum from another website, the address of that website as well as additional information related to your visit. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer the Forum.

**Information Collected**

We collect the email addresses of consumers who communicate with us via email.

Any information provided by consumers becomes our property once received by us and may be used and disclosed as permitted in this Policy.

We may aggregate your personal information with others' information and prepare reports on Forum usage or other factors for distribution to others. Those reports are aggregated and include no personally identifying information. Finally, we may use your personal information to send you email or postal communications regarding products or services offered by us or by third parties with whom we have relationships in which we think you may be interested. We do not share, sell, trade or rent your personal information to third parties for unknown reasons. You may at any time choose not to receive promotional emails from us by contacting us at [ admin@pomsinoz.com](mailto:admin@pomsinoz.com). Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may continue to contact you for the purpose of communicating information relating to this Forum, as well as to facilitate, complete, or confirm any transaction that you may enter into or responding to your inquiry or request.

**Use of Forums**

If you choose to transmit, submit or post information through the forum's chat rooms, bulletin boards or other forums (the "Forums"), we will collect that information you provide. We retain this information as necessary to resolve disputes, provide customer support and troubleshoot problems as permitted by law and pursuant to our Terms of Use.

**Cookies**

We may place "cookies" on your personal computer. "Cookies" are small identifiers sent from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive, similar to a license plate, that help us to recognize you if you visit our webforum again. Also, our Forum uses cookies to track how you found our Forum. Cookies are not designed to be used to get data from your hard drive, your e-mail or any other personal data about you. To protect your privacy, we do not use cookies to store or transmit any personal information about you on the Internet. You can reject cookies by changing your browser settings. Please note, however, that if you reject our cookies, it is possible that some web pages may not properly load, your access to certain information might be denied or you might have to enter information about yourself more than once.

**Security**

This Forum has reasonable security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

**Third Party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our webForum. These companies use non-personally identifiable information regarding your visit to this webForum and other Forums, such as the user IP address, pages viewed, date and time of your visit, and number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), to serve ads to you on this Forum and other Forums that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to this Forum, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

Specifically, Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this webForum. Google´s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to this webForum and other webForums on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network [privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Contacting the Web Forum**

Please be aware that we may change our Privacy Policy from time to time. If we do, we will update this Privacy Policy at our webforum, so be sure to check back here frequently.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Forum, or your dealings with this Web Forum, you can contact: [ admin@pomsinoz.com](mailto:admin@pomsinoz.com).

Revised: 01/06/2011

www.pomsinoz.com
